There's a sign at the entrance
to this neighborhood.
Anyone past this point, who causes pain
Who brings destruction
Who holds evil in their heart will be
purged by Bofurin without exception!
A sign posted by the strong.
BOFURIN
Bofurin is led by students of Furin High
who fight to protect this town.
FURIN
FURIN HIGH SCHOOL
Sakura came from out of town
and entered Furin High.
BOFURIN
On his first day of school,
during a patrol, he saved a middle school
student who was being chased by men.
However, it turned out the men
who were chasing the middle school boy
were on Team Shishitoren,
who proclaim to be devotees of power.
Sakura's action sparked a series of events
ending in all-out war between
Furin High and Shishitoren.
Choji Tomiyama, the leader of Shishitoren,
suggested a 5-on-5 team match.
If Tomiyama were to win against
Furin's representative Hajime Umemiya,
Umemiya and Furin High would fall
into the hands of Shishitoren.
To challenge themselves
with battles they can't lose,
Sakura and the gang
headed over to Shishitoren turf.
Welcome! Come on in!
Yeah. We're comin' in.
Come on now, this way!
Hurry, hurry!
Choji, no need to run.
YAKITORI
OKONOMIYAKI
In any case...
It's all pubs here.
Shishitoren's turf has a lot of pubs.
This is the biggest pub district of them all.
I hear it's very lively at night.
Though, I hear it gets pretty dodgy, too.
Anyway...
Why the hell are you here?
You're not fighting a one-on-one.
Wh-Why? Because I'm also involved
as I was there at the scene.
Besides, I'm still a member of Bofurin.
Even if I can't protect people like how you guys can,
I'd like to be able to protect myself.
Please let me learn.
Do as you like.
Sakura-kun, you blush really easily!
Sh-Shut up!
You shut up!
Sheesh. Why can't you
at least be a little nervous?
And you should relax your shoulders a bit.
Sakura-san! I'll massage you before
your fight so that you'll be in top condition!
But you know...
it's so promising.
- I don't need one!
- Don't be modest!
Hey! Hurry, hurry!
Over here!
I formally...
welcome you...
to Shishitoren's lair.
the ORIon
Ori?
Shishitoren's hangout is a movie theater named
"The Orion" that went out of business.
Nowadays, they call it Ori, meaning "Cage."
Okay, let's do this!
Time for fighters to enter the arena!
Hurry up and start!
That's Umemiya.
That Hiragi next to him?
C'mon, show us your mugs!
Who're the punks in the back?
Dunno.
I see, I get it.
Indeed, this is a "cage" of wild beasts.
Can we make it home?
Can we make it back alive?
You came here to study, didn't ya?
Keep your eyes forward.
Now, guys...
It's time for our super-fun
one-on-one matches to begin!
Sheesh, he turned this into a gala.
Listen up, guys.
It turned into a big deal, but the main event
is my one-on-one against Tomiyama.
Your wins or losses won't count.
So feel at ease when you get up there!
Screw you.
Whether it counts or not...
I don't intend to lose.
Ya heard 'im.
You really are a reliable one!
Now, Ume-chan! Let's do it!
Come on!
Oh no, no. There's no way
that the team captains goes first.
Whaaa!?
Cap'n, can I go first?
That long mop's been shootin' me
dirty looks and gettin' on my nerves.
Oh my, Sugishita-kun, you're being
passionately requested!
Well, why not?
Hey.
I haven't settled my score with you yet.
But if you're gonna lose to pathetic losers
like these, I don't wanna fight you ever again.
Hey, are you listening?
I'm tellin' ya not to lose!
- Get 'im!
- Arima!
- Kill 'im!
- Go get 'im!
Arima... Arima...
Oh, here it is!
Yukinari Arima.
He seems like quite the heavy hitter.
He's broken several ribs with one blow!?
Now, now. Sugishita-kun is basically
the same kind, so it should be okay.
Oh, no.
I'd feel sorry for him to be put
in the same league as that guy.
Damn.
You really have irritating eyes.
Hey Umemiya, what's the matter?
Don't look away during a fight, ya moron.
Need the "san."
Weaksauce.
That's Umemiya-san, ya moron.
Come on, that can't be real.
Man, seriously?
Arima got destroyed.
You know that guy?
Never seen him. A first-year?
O-One punch.
This can't be happening.
That's amazing! You're really built tough!
What's your name?
Fight me next!
Hey, Choji.
You sit tight and wait.
Not only is there a lack of concern
for the guy who lost,
but they complimented the opponent.
I felt it back then, too.
Those guys really have a few screws loose.
Hey, welcome back!
Man, you really are
as aggressive as always!
You okay where you got punched?
You've always had a tough body, huh?
He got punched, so stop that.
Sugishita-san is amazing.
He's perfectly fine despite
getting smacked like that.
Well, that's how he is.
Sakura-san, you're not surprised at all.
Well, I did face him once.
Sakura-kun, so you do accept Sugishita-kun.
N-No way! I'm just saying
I know he's built tough!
- What's with that face?! Hey!
- Right.
That's not what I mean, damn it!
I'll punch you!
Kame-chan, how would you
defeat Long-Hair-kun?
I just said he's built tough!
I didn't mean anything other than that!
Kame-chan?
Yeah.
All right! Next up! Next!
Hey, hey. You two over there.
Get rid of that.
- Hurry, please!
- 'Kay.
Man, he's heavy.
No way we can drag him to the edge.
Let's just dump him here.
Sheesh. He always acts big,
but this is how he ends up?
Idiot.
Serves you right.
Th-That's horrible.
Hey.
Quit yappin' near me.
All of ya. Never say
you're devotees of power ever again.
It embarrasses me
just watching you, wimps.
Sakura-kun.
It won't matter what you say.
Kids like them won't understand
until they're defeated.
Then you're gonna make me understand?
Wha...
Hey.
That guy's opponent isn't you.
Stand back.
C'mon, c'mon, next!
Next up! Who's up next?
Then I...
Don't be so stupid.
It's clearly my turn next.
Who you callin' stupid!?
Right, little boy?
You seem stressed out.
Why don't we get some exercise?
Oh! Numa-chan, good luck!
- Y-Yeah. Get 'im, Kanuma!
- Fight! Fight!
Sakura-kun.
What?
When you mentioned you came here
to take the top spot,
I thought you were kinda stupid.
Have you been picking a fight
with me? Cuz I'll take you on!
Calm down.
I wasn't, sorry. I thought your words
were empty and meaningless.
But your words and actions have a spine.
And I think that's awesome.
So, I'll do my best so I can keep up with you.
Hurry up and go already!
Kanuma!
Get 'im!
Send 'im flying!
What kinda guy is he?
Oh, you mean Kanuma-san?
Please hold on a second.
No, not that guy.
Oh, you mean Suo-san?
Of course, he was famous for being strong
from back in middle school.
I can tell he's strong
just by looking at him! Anything else?
What? You can tell by looking?
That doesn't matter right now!
The thing is...
His fame is all I've got.
No specific stories like who he won against.
Huh? Are you serious?
Indeed, I've heard of his name quite a bit.
But I don't know any details about him.
He went to a different middle school, too.
I didn't know much about Suo, either.
But I understood when I met him.
He's a kind gentleman.
Thanks to you guys, Arima is...
What's this?
You can get angry for your buddies?
That's so different from the other day.
I...
I've been hangin' with Arima for a long time.
My brother went down.
It's only natural that I'm pissed off!
You whine only when you're the victim.
You're just like an impatient child.
Kind, you say?
It waz so tuff for you huh, wittle boy?
Is that the face of a gentleman?
Tantrums looks cute
only up to grade school at best.
Now, why don't we move on up
to adulthood together?
Wh-What just happened?
He instantaneously got behind me?
How he moves...
He's dabbled in something.
Then...
I just have to punch so fast
so he can't dodge it!
That was quite a nasty spill.
Damn you.
A question for you.
What do you think you need
to become an adult?
...why don't we move on up
to adulthood together?
What the hell is this garbled nonsense?
Th-That's amazing.
It looks like his opponent
is stumbling around on his own.
Idiot!
Take this seriously!
Why you lettin' him toy with ya?
Cut it out already, Kanuma!
You mockin' us or something?
They talk as they please.
You think I need to cut it out?
I push, I pull, I grab.
He parries them all instantly.
Then why don't you guys
try going up against this guy?
He wasn't just an ordinary gentleman.
He doesn't even have a shred of kindness.
He has a craptastic personality.
He's tormenting an inferior opponent
and making a fool out of him.
You're being shown your skill gap forever.
If I was him, it'd make me wanna die.
I-I see.
Though I'd never end up like that.
It's definitely brutal.
Well...
After seeing the Shishitoren guys,
he surely had some thoughts about them.
I didn't expect him
to be this emotional about it.
You know, that's probably because...
he probably got affected
by someone near him.
Come to think...
I'll do my best.
Hey.
Yes?
How can I get him
to seriously spar with me?
Huh? Why?
Damn you!
Come on, stand up already!
You mockin' us, Kanuma?
And you say you're serious about this?
Huh? No way.
If I can't make something happen...
It's about time...
that you're starting to figure out the answer.
What you're thinking right now...
Not... Not... happen... this...
Not happening! Not happening!
This is not happening!
Let me guess what's going
through your head right now.
An image of you becoming that person
you used to ridicule.
That's the answer to the question.
What you need to become an adult is...
an imagination.
Now...
Once you got that down,
the ball's in your court!
Let's move on to the next step
before you forget!
What do you think you need to make
that imagination more solid than it is now?
You need the imagination to become reality.
Wait—
Stop.
That's enough.
Sorry, Eyepatch-kun. Can you step down?
Huh? Is it over?
Uh, n-no... Wh-Why...
Don't humiliate us any further.
Oh wait, it wouldn't be a humiliation...
as you're not one of us anymore.
Becoming an adult
means being able to empathize.
To do that,
you need imagination and experience.
Good for you.
I think you at least
stepped up one level, right?
A GENTLEMAN
Shishitoren's hideout
really has quite the ambience.
Is this a movie theater
that went outta business?
Oh, I've heard about
the shark movie on this poster!
Wait. This is another shark movie.
This one is about sharks, too.
Hey! This one over here, too!
Sharks.
I think I have an idea
why they went outta business.